Deborah Keme

312-804-3951 | deborahkeme@gmail.com

<u>Profile</u>: Computer Science student with applied knowledge of Python, Mobile Development Apps, and understanding of solving complex conceptual problems using research. Held part-time and summer jobs that challenged my critical thinking, communication, and presentation skills. Serve as a board member at clubs and non-profit organizations.

Work Experience

Africa Now Association | Board Member/Marketing Strategist

November 2018 - Present

- Increase both Facebook & Instagram following by 400+, 782 shares, and 1,000 likes
- Collect data from 2018 conference utilizing it to promote this year's conference
- Present power-point pitch to UW Sustainability Fund and succeeded in obtaining \$13,400 in funding which was allocated to speaker, social media promotion, and venue funds
- Experiment with website design for our central webpage

African Women Business Alliance | Operations Manager

January 2019 - September 2019

- Integrate wholistic approach to the Business Development program by implementing child-care, linguistics, and transportation factors
- Assign task of coordinating 3 seasonal marketplace events hosting 40 vendors and 150+ attendees
- Utilize Excel Pivot, tables, graphs, to organize and filter cohort's information
- Operate closely with Founder/CEO to budget capacity building amounting to \$30,000

University Tutors for Seattle Schools | Algebra I & Geometry Tutor

February 2019 - June 2019

- Adapt to Public School teaching by working closely to math teachers and facilitating study group sessions for freshman/sophomore high-school students
- Deliver lessons in perspective classrooms to help students engage with math and build personal relationships with students in order to encourage them to come in for help outside of classroom setting
- Listen for feedback from teachers and students to better use skills that align with their learning abilities

Education

Seattle Central College

Spring Quarter 2018- Winter Quarter 2020

Associate in Sciences— Computer Science

Drexel University | Philadelphia, PA

Fall Quarter 2017 - Winter Quarter 2018

Involvement & Activities

<u>Space Apps Seattle Hackathon Challenge</u> | Lead Engineer/Designer <u>She's Coding Hackathon</u> | UX Experience Designer

Computer Science Club | Member May 2019- Present

Mathematics Engineering Science Achievement (MESA) | Member

September 2018- Present

Impact Hub Seattle | Volunteer

October 2018-May 2019